Guide to the George Mason University Libraries records, 1949-2008
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 3: Reports and Publications, 1960-2007
  - Subseries 3.2: Reports, 1960-2001
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS), Fulfilling our commitments: Volume 1: Compliance report: Section 5: Educational support sus (library), 2001 March 1 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS) report, 1986-1989 (Box 57, Folder 12)
      1 of 6
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS) report, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      2 of 6
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS) report, 1989-1990 (Box 57, Folder 14)
      3 of 6
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS) report, 1986-1990 (Box 57, Folder 15)
      4 of 6
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS) report, 1989-1990 (Box 57, Folder 16)
      5 of 6
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS) report, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      6 of 6
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS) report, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS) self study update, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Safety and risk management, 1991-1995 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Salaries, 1980-1981 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - School of Library and Information Sciences proposal, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - SDI report, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Self study report, library administration, 1979-1980 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Self study, 1977-1981 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Self study, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Self study update, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Serial Committee report, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Services and public relations suggestions, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Staff senate annual report, 1999-2001 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - State board for the certification of librarians, 1980-1986 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Statement from GMU library regarding the future, 1989 March (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Statewide needs assessment of library services in Virginia, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Statistics, administrative statistical information, 1972-1977 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Statistics, administrative statistical information, 1973-1976 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Statistics, annual statistics, 1963-1964 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Statistics, Fenwick Library statistical information, 1983-1986 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Statistics, GMC Library outside circulation, 1967 November-1970 January (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Statistics, GMU Fenwick Library, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Statistics, reference department statistical reports, 1995-1997 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Statistics, statistical summary for first half 1985 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Status of women and minorities report, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Strategy for development, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Storage, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Student affairs division annual report, 1979-1977 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Study to develop a long-range library automation and network development plan for the commonwealth of Virginia - Phase 1 report, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Suggestion book, 1975-1981 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Suggestions for Fenwick library, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Summary of discussion with university police, 1992 July 27 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Survey, computer-based services survey draft, 1988 July (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Survey, Council of Higher Education survey, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Survey, Hegis report, Hew library survey, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Survey, Hegis report, Hew library survey, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Survey, information service survey, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Survey, IPEDS, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Survey, Law library questionnaire and GMU library survey, 1999-2000 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Survey, library survey, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Survey, library survey, 2000 February 2 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Survey, library survey results and student petition for new 24 hour library hours, 1991 April (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Survey, library users satisfaction survey, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Survey, Palinet Planning Committee, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Survey, reference, periodicals, microforms survey comments, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Survey, reference, periodicals survey and results, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Survey, state of library, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Task force computer literacy, 1989 March (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Task force on academic integrity, "Instilling academic integrity" report, 2001 May 17 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Telephone sample report, 1991 May 2 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Transition plan, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Travel reports, 1979-1980 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Trust fund, equipment trust fund, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Undergraduate multicultural library collection, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Undergraduate report, 1989 February (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - University libraries (description of GMU libraries), 2001 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - University library systems, 1981-1993 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Virginia governor's conference on library and information services, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Virginia governor's conference on library and information services, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Virginia governor's conference on library and information services, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - The Virginia plan, 1974 January (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Virginia plan for academic library cooperation, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Volumes reports, 1960-1965 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Volumes reports, 1966-1971 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Volumes reports, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Volumes reports, 1972-1974 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Volumes reports, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Volumes reports, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Volumes reports, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Volumes reports, 1986 July-1987 June (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Volumes reports, volume and cost report, 1988-1989 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 3.3: Meeting minutes, 1972-2002
    Includes meeting minutes from division head meetings, faculty senate, graduate council meetings and others.
    - Academic affairs meetings, 1980-1984 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Access services Committee, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Activity heads minutes, 1982 June 2 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Administration, activities meeting notes, 1976-1977 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - College of arts and sciences, minutes of the faculty, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Deans and directors meeting, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Deans and directors meeting, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Deans and directors meeting, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Deans and directors meeting, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Deans and directors meeting, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Deans and directors meeting, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Deans and directors meeting, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Deans and directors meeting, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Deans and directors meeting, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Deans and directors meeting, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Department heads meeting minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Departmental heads of staff meetings, 1987-1989 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Departmental heads of staff meetings, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Departmental staff meeting, 1989 June 7, 1990 March 14 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Division heads meetings minutes, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Division heads meeting, 1982-1983 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Division heads minutes, announcements, 1982-1985 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Division heads meetings minutes, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Division heads meetings minutes, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Division heads meetings minutes, 1985 July (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Division heads meetings minutes, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Division heads retreat, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Faculty senate minutes, 1983 January 26 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - General faculty meeting, 1975-1981 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - General faculty meeting minutes, 1987 April 29 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - George Johnson notes, 1989 March (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - George Mason University Arlington II, Town Hall meetings, 2007 September 18 (Box 210, Folder 2)
      DVD
    - Graduate council minutes, 1975 November 7-1977 November 4 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Graduate council minutes, 1977-1981 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Graduate faculty, 1972-1981 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Information technology meeting (O'Connor), 1996 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Library senior staff meeting minutes, 1986 October-1990 December (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Mason link, 1993-1995 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Mason link, 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Mason link meeting, 1997 September 9 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Mason scholars, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous meeting notes, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Northern Virginia health sciences librarians' group minutes of meeting, 1987 December 3 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Office of Provost staff meetings (formerly academic affairs), 1985-1988 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Policy and planning council, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Policy and planning council agenda, 1995 September 20 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Professional meetings, conferences, 1979-1980 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Reference department meeting minutes, 1996 May 15 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Selector's meeting, 1989 December 6 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Senior management team meetings, 1998-1999 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - SNAUB, meeting notes, emails, and other materials, 1994-1995 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Solinet meeting minutes, 1980 May (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Solinet/OCLC meetings, Board of Directors meetings, 1980-1987 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Staff meetings, 1987-1991 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Staff meetings, 1987-1995 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Staff senate minutes, 2001 October 18 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - State networking users advisory council, 1979-1983 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - University relations' minutes, information networking meetings, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - University scholars, 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 3.4: Publications, 1964-2007
    Includes the publications Added Entries, Federal One, Full Text, and Library Notes as well as brochures and other newletters produced by the Library staff.
    - Added entries, 1985 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Added entries, 1986 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Added entries, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Added entries, Fenwick library newsletter, 1987-1989 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Added entries, 1988 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Added entries, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Added entries, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Added entries, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Added entries, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - An introductory workbook to Fenwick Library, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Audiovisual video holdings, 1989-1990 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Automation newsletter, 1985 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Basic information systems and services by Jamie Coniglio, 1994 Fall (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Brochures, 1979-1987 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Brochures and publications from Arlington Campus Library, 1997-1998 (Box 210, Folder 1)
      Arlington Campus Libraries News
    - Collection development newsletter, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Copyright news, 2002 Fall (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Copyright news, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Directory of special programs, projects, disadvantaged student, 1977 December (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Electronics for the library, computers, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Faculty guide to GMU libraries, "Take Cover!", 1981 August (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Faculty journal editors, 2003-2004 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Federal one, 1975-1982 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Federal One, volume 3, no. 2, 1978 September (Box 68, Folder 2)
      Original copy
    - Federal One, ideas, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Federal One, original logo art, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Federal One, volume 4, no. 1, 1979 January (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Federal One, volume 4, no. 2, 1979 June (Box 68, Folder 6)
      Copy
    - Federal One, basic information and mailing list, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Federal One, next issue, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Federal One, 5:1, 1980 February (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Federal One, 5:1, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      Xerox originals
    - Federal One, 5:1, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      Originals
    - Fenwick at a glance, 1988-1993 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Fenwick at a glance, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Fenwick focus survey, undated (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Fenwick focus, 1978-1979 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Fenwick follies, 1978-1982 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Fenwick for beginners, 1983-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Fenwick for beginners, 1984-1985 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Fenwick for beginners, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Fenwick library newsletter, 1979-1985 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Fenwick library newsletter, 1984-1985 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - "Fenwick friends in living color", circulation, 1982 July 15 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Fenwick productions, "Fun with elevators", 1982 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Fenwick productions, "Fun with Flossie and Sadie", 1982 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Full Text, 1991-1992 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Full Text, 1993-1994 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Full Text, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Full Text, 1997-1998 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Full Text, 1997-1999 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Full Text, 1998 Fall-1999 Fall (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Full Text, 1999 Spring (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Full Text, special collections and archives, 1999 Fall-2000 Fall (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Full Text, 1999 Winter-2000 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Full Text, Spring 2000 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Full Text, Summer 2000 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Full Text, 2000-2001 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Full Text, 2001 Fall (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Full Text, 2001 Winter (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Full Text, copy, 2001 Spring-2002 Spring (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Full Text, 2001 Winter-2002 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Full Text, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Full Text, no. 159, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Full Text, no. 160-161, 2004 Spring-2004 Fall (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Full Text, 2005 Summer-2007 Fall (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - F.Y.I., Arlington library newsletter, 1995-1996 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Generic fall faculty letter, 1989 August 4 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - GMC library bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Guide to Information technology services, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Library handouts, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Library Link, volume 1, issue 1 to volume 2, issue 4, 2002 Summer-2004 Spring (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Library Link, 2005-2006 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Library newsletters, 1976-1979 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Library Notes, volume 1, 1964-1965 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Library Notes, volume 2, 1965-1966 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Library Notes, volume 3, copy 1, 1966-1967 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Library Notes, volume 4, copy 1, 1967-1968 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Library Notes, volume 5, 1968-1969 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Library Notes, volume 6, copy 2, 1969-1970 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Library Notes, volume 7, copy 1, 1970-1971 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Library Notes, volume 8, 1-3, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Library Notes, volume 9, copy 2, no. 1-4, 1972-1973 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Library Notes, volume 10, no. 1-5, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Library Notes, volume 11, no. 1-3, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Library Notes, volume 12, no. 1-2, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Library Notes, volume 13, no. 1-3, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Library Notes "Flash!", 1977 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Library Notes, volume 14, no. 1, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Library Notes, volume 15, no. 1, 1978 December 1 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Library Notes correspondence, 1981-1988 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - News from Fenwick Library, 1987-1989 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Newsletters, 1990-1995 (Box 72, Folder 12)
      Focus, ICAR newsletter, Matrix, VSLA news, Connections, 1 of 2
    - Newsletters, 1990-1993 (Box 72, Folder 13)
      Focus, ICAR newsletter, Matrix, VSLA news, Connections, 2 of 2
    - Pamphlet, undated (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Posner article, undated (Box 72, Folder 15)
      "Future: or library and the 21st, or will robots replace student shelvers, or does one Floppy disc equal one librarian"
    - Posner - In-Flight Index, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Pro-Libris, 1989 Fall (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Proposal for Fenwick newsletter, 1980 December 14 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Publications, professional, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - TIP sheets, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Virginia Foundation for the Humanities newsletter, 1978-1979 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Virginia Library Association newsletter, 1976-1984 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Virginia State Library news, 1975-1987 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Subseries 3.5: Publicity and research, 1967-1995
    Contains newspaper and magazine articles featuring the libraries at George Mason and especially the Federal Theatre Project. Research articles focus on library science, professional development, and public relations.
    - Articles, importance of library information, 1990-1995 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Articles, information technology and online services for research, 1992-1993 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Broadside, library article, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Broadside, 1989, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Copyright issues, 1989 March (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - DAEMON link, 1989 March (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Federal Theatre Project, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Federal Theatre Project, 1930s Drama from the W.P.A. FTP, circa 1977 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Federal Theatre Project, American Society for Theatre Research newsletter, volume 6, no. 1, Winter 1979 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Federal Theatre Project, American Theatre Association: 39th annual convention, 1975 August 10-13 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Federal Theatre Project, American Theatre Association: Theatre news, volume 8, no. 7, 1976 April (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Federal Theatre Project, Anthropology and the Theatre of the Mind, Judi Mason hits; Broadway and Glamour, 1977 April (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Federal Theatre Project, The Black Scholar, volume 10, no. 10, 1979 July-August (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Federal Theatre Project, Correspondence and meetings, 1978-1980 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Federal Theatre Project, Disabled USA - seeing in tandem: participating as an equal, volume 1, no. 9, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Federal Theatre Project, Dramatics: the Magazine of the International Thespian Society, no. 4, 1977 March-April (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Federal Theatre Project, Encore: the Magazine of the Theatre, 1979 April (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Federal Theatre Project, GMU Today, volume 6, no. 2, 1980 Fall (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Federal Theatre Project puppets, 1980 June (Box 73, Folder 19)
      Kennedy Center program
    - Federal Theatre Project, 1976-1978 (Box 73, Folder 20)
      Newspaper clippings
    - Federal Theatre Project, 1978-1979 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Federal Theatre Project, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 22)
      Newspaper and book clippings
    - Federal Theatre Project, 1979-1980 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      Non-GMU printed copies, photographs
    - Federal Theatre Project, original discovery, 1974-1975 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Federal Theatre Project, 1976-1978 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      Press releases
    - Federal Theatre Project, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      Press releases Broadside
    - Federal Theatre Project, 1979-1980 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      Press releases In House
    - Federal Theatre Project, 1978-1979 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      Ppress releases, non-GMU
    - Federal Theatre Project, 1978-1979 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      Printed copies Broadside
    - Federal Theatre Project, 1978-1980 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      Printed copies In House
    - Federal Theatre Project, 1978-1980 (Box 74, Folder 9)
      Printed copies other GMU publications
    - Federal Theatre Project, Professional development: Sonneck Society newsletter, "The FTP's musical productions", 1987 Fall (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Federal Theatre Project, Saturday review, 1976 September 18 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Federal Theatre Project, Stereo Review, volume 38, no. 3, 1977 March (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Federal Theatre Project, Tabs: Stage Lighting International, 1977 Summer (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Federal Theatre Project, Theatre Design and Technology, United States Institute for Theatre Technology, 1978 Fall (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Federal Theatre Project, Theatre news: American Theatre Association, volume 11, no. 1, 1978 September-October (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Federal Theatre Project, Washington Guide to the Arts, 1979 December (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Free, adult, uncensored, 1973-1979 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - General publicity, 1978-1979 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - GMU library communication, xerox extra, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - GMU SCHEV: University of 21st century, article, 1988 December (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Harvard library, HOLLIS, 1989 March (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Library, 1989 February (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - News items, 1967-1973 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Northwestern University core library, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Orbit publicity memo, 1984 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Professional development reading, 1980 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Public relations, other collections at GMU, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Publicity, ideas, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Resources for American Literary Study, volume 7, no. 2, 1977 Autumn (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Rethinking the library, volume 2, 1990s (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Special collections, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Special collections, 1980 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - UCLA library technology, 1989 March (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Virginia governor news clips, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Virginia state funds for library planning, 1989 February (Box 75, Folder 20)
- Series 4: Committees and collaborations, 1960-2004
  This series consists of files originating from library committees and files concerning collaborations within the University and with other institutions undertaken by the library. Arranged alphabetically, then chronologically.
  - Academic Computing Advisory Committee, 1980-1985 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Academic Computing Advisory Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Access Services Planning Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Ad Hoc Committee, staffing, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Association, 1976-1981 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Association, 1983-1994 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Alumni relations, 1980-1981 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - American Type Culture Collection (ATCC) Committee, 1995-1998 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - American Type Culture Collection (ATCC) Committee, 1997-2003 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Reference meeting (PWL), ATCC Committee, 2001 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Appointments Committee, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - An address by Omer L. Hirst before Arlington Committee of 100, 1960 April 13 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Arlington Campus Library Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Arlington Campus Library Committee, meeting minutes, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Arlington Campus Library Committee, policies, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Arlington Campus Library Committee, policies, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Arlington Campus Library information, 2003-2006 (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - Arlington Campus Library monthly summaries, 2004-2005 (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - Arlington Campus Library site goals, 2004-2005 (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - Arlington Campus Library staff meetings, 2004-2006 (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - Arlington Campus Library web team, 2002 (Box 204, Folder 5)